Just one, two, three, go.
Done, right?
Awesome.
Yuning.
Can't do it without you!
Alright, come on.
Play it.
Point forward.
Then point this way, and then...
Make a heart.
Good.
Why are you
moving the same arm and leg?
You say
You say you
Wait, listen to me.
Let's just use this.
Let's go with yours.
Like that "washing hair with no water" one.
We need to make up a story.
Right, that works.
We'll definitely remember it this way.
Then we'll have it memorized.
The first move is left, right, up.
Not making a story for this one, right?
So the opening pose is...
I'm here.
Going for a shower at 3 p.m.
He goes for a shower at 3 p.m.
My brain can't handle this story.
Don't.
It's 3 p.m.
No way, bro.
I tried your method.
But this just makes it harder.
I have to memorize the words too.
This is even more confusing.
Okay.
Yuning, let's just go with your way.
Right.
Just call out the moves.
You just lead the dance.
Alright.
No problem.
Let's go.
Let's continue.
Sweep the floor.
Left hand.
Get away from me.
Go away.
Wash hair.
Wash body.
Swipe again.
Then left hand again.
No, no, no.
Wipe the window.
Then wipe left, wipe right.
Then spin around.
The window is clean.
Done wiping.
And we're done.
Awesome.
See? We're all dance geniuses.
Seriously.
No need to spare our feelings. Wait, no.
Splash the face.
No.
Head.
I'm sure we won't mess up.
We know it so well now.
Come on.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start.
Okay, stretch.
Then stretch right.
You, you, you.
You say you.
Good, walk backwards.
Okay, then sweep the floor.
Left hand, then swipe.
I thought I could get away with it.
Uncle Nai is out.
Uncle Nai...
The back of his head got splashed flat!
That was brutal!
Just once.
Everyone else.
Three, two, one, go!
Stretch!
You, you, you...
Phone number!
Stretch!
You, you, you...
I...
Where did I go wrong?
Why is it the two of us?
I don't know.
Ready.
Let's go.
Love Even If I Die
Oh my god!
Not to the fullest...
I'm doomed.
Love!
Not satisfying unless to the fullest.
What a stark contrast.
Just like that.
Let me take your heart.
Love Even If I Die
A "true god" has descended.
Oh my god.
Yeye, you're my boss.
Don't laugh.
It's Zhou Ye's first time playing, right?
Then tell me this...
Love Even If I Die
Not satisfying unless to the fullest.
Hurry!
Love Even If I Die
Not satisfying unless to the fullest.
Keep going.
Just remember to keep going.
I'm so nervous right now.
I'll sing seriously. Come on.
Keep going. Just remember to keep going.
If the sea could
Keep going.
bring back past love.
If the sea could
Keep going.
Sharpening scissors! Sharpening knives!
Right, that's what I thought of too.
It sounds so similar.
If the sea could
Right.
bring back past love.
Keep going.
He sings exactly like you, right?
Then he's really good.
My passion is like
a fire, burning the whole
He didn't even keep going.
My passion is like
a fire, burning the whole
That's all the lyrics I know.
Keep going.
Okay.
Summer, summer quietly
passes, leaving little secrets behind
Come on.
Lin Yi.
Make a sound at least!
Okay.
Shall we start?
Yes.
Hurts.
Loving until it hurts...
Hurts...
Loving until it hurts, hurting until I cry, crying until I'm tired.
Nice. That's on pitch.
What song is this?
An addictive poison re-
An addictive poison, it repeatedly
deceives me.
I tell myself
to let go.
Close my eyes, let you go, burn the diary.
Alright.
Come.
Hello everyone.
We are a
group from Beijing.
We'd like to perform
"Beaming with Joy"
Music Director:
Zhou Ye.
Stage Effects:
Li Naiwen.
Stage Director: Sun Honglei.
Sound Director: Guo Jingfei.
Everyone,
our honor depends on this.
The show begins now.
A play. Here we go.
Okay.
Come on, bow.
I'm on the side.
Bow to the audience.
Let's get a beat going first.
Five, six, seven, eight.
We can do this.
Zhou Ye's got some skills
Not bad
This mic sounds a bit muddy
We should've sung first
This mic isn't doing so great right now
It really feels like a karaoke room
Karaoke room
It affects the result
Result
Hello everyone, we're
Jurassic Park
Three T-Rexes and a handler
Nice
Good
Alright
So I'm the band's
Lead singer and bassist
I'm the female lead singer of this band
And the face of the group
I'm the band's kick drum
Kick drum
Drummer Chen Xingxu
I'm the band's synthesizer
Also known as the synthesizer
See, they're super confident right from the start
Now we'll bring you a
Pure a cappella song
"Beaming with Joy"
Dedicated to all of you
Remember to scream, everyone
But don't scream for too long, you might pass out
Ladies and gentlemen
Welcome to
The excitement is about to begin
Welcome to our party
Starting now
Too much right and wrong in love
Coming to a "Beaming with Joy" occasion
Mixing his impulse and her loneliness
Regardless of the consequences
You say
I want results
Turn around and start over
Guys, girls, don't wait any longer
Freedom, freedom, we want freedom now
Thank you.
Chopping veggies with a twisted ankle.
One chop, two chops, three chops.
It's our turn.
Four chops.
Come back.
One chop, two chops, three chops, four chops.
Okay, step forward.
Stand in a line.
I'm getting a little tired.
Right?
Can't argue with that.
What's this?
Robot dog
It's not even falling off.
I'm young and brash
Don't kick it.
Try it.
It might work. Try it.
Come on.
Stand it up.
Don't hold it.
Protect!
Protect our big bro!
Wake up!
What?
Close enough.
Very pretty.
Absolutely beautiful.
No problem.
So playful.
Bow
Ladies
Gentlemen
Forward
Back
Spin
Forward
Back
Ladies half turn
"Love Bridge"
Okay
Pretty good
Sing this song innocently
Innocent
The patch of sky above
Innocent!
Bro, innocent!
How about this?
Okay
Twist
But your feet have to twist too
Your feet have to twist too
The patch of sky above
Is a man's patch of sky
Once beneath the starry sky
A dreaming youth
Lighting Up the Stars
How was it?
Love seeing you frown so tight
Call me a coward
Your expression is more than
Friendly flirting
Is Lin Yi singing Huadan?
Huadan
Your expression is too
Lonely ti...
Wrong
Lin Yi
There's a unique
and exclusive specialness
You're singing Huadan
Can we isolate that and have a listen?
Give us a solo bit
What key? I don't know this key
Seeing you frown so tight
Call me a coward
Vocal warm-up
Love seeing you frown so tight
Call me a coward
Okay
Saying goodbye to you
Because I might never see you again
Tomorrow I will leave
Familiar places and you
As we part, my tears just fall
I will firmly remember your face
I will cherish the memories you gave
These days in my heart
Will never be erased
I cannot promise you
Whether I will come back
Not looking back
Walking on without looking back
Spin slower!
Come on, roll over me
Is that a good idea?
Head
Okay, come on
You get up first
Right
Come on
Someone count the beats
One, two, three, go!
No, it's not over
There's more
I'm halfway through chopping the veggies
Chop
One, two, three, go!
Shake your clothes
Shake your shoulders
Okay, shoot!
Alright.
Alright, first move.
That's amazing!
I can't live without you!
Annie, I call out to you with my life!
Loving you forever!
Brother Fei is so cute!
You sang the loudest,
but you sang
the worst!
Take Kaikai, he just said he can't sing,
but
he sang the best.
Really?
Yeah.
To me,
Wen is supposed to be highly musical.
But this time you sang the...
You've never been so mean to me.
We take music very seriously, okay?
Xingxu is actually pretty good.
Really pretty good.
He didn't quite catch the rhythm at first.
But later,
following my rhythm,
following the music's rhythm,
he found the beat.
Very good.
Really quite good.